export const HorrorMoviesQuestions = [
    {
        question: "What 2008 film by Bryan Bertino was influenced by the Manson murders?",
        answers: [
                'Cloverfield',
                'Asylum',
                'The Strangers',
                'The Dead Outside' 
          ], 
          correctAnswer: 'The Strangers'
      },
      {
        question: "What state is the 2007 film 'Thirty Days of Night' set in?",
        answers: [
                'Alaska',
                'Alabama',
                'Montana',
                'Mississippi' 
          ], 
          correctAnswer: 'Alaska'
      },
      {
        question: "What actress plays portrayed protagonist Grace Stewart in 2001's 'The Others' set in?",
        answers: [
                'Elaine Cassidy',
                'Alakina Mann',
                'Fionnula Flanagan',
                'Nicole Kidman' 
          ], 
          correctAnswer: 'Nicole Kidman'
      },
      {
        question: "What H.P. Lovecraft novella influenced the 2016 film 'The Void'?",
        answers: [
                'The Color Out of Space',
                'At the Mountains of Madness',
                'Dagon',
                'The Outsider' 
          ], 
          correctAnswer: 'At the Mountains of Madness'
      },
      {
        question: "In the 2007 movie 'Trick or Treat,' what are the four group of women revealed to be?",
        answers: [
                'Witches',
                'Vampires',
                'Werewolves',
                'Zombies' 
          ], 
          correctAnswer: 'Werewolves'
      },
      {
        question: "The two detectives in the 1995 film 'Se7en' are played by Brad Pitt and what other actor?",
        answers: [
                'Morgan Freeman',
                'Kevin Spacey',
                'Richard Roundtree',
                'John McGinley' 
          ], 
          correctAnswer: 'Morgan Freeman'
      },
      {
        question: "The 2007 film 'The Mist' was based on the novella of the same name by what author?",
        answers: [
                'Clive Barker',
                'Anne Rice',
                'Steven King',
                'Shirley jackson' 
          ], 
          correctAnswer: 'Steven King'
      },
      {
        question: "In the 2002 film 'The Ring', how many days does a viewer have to live after watching the cursed videotape??",
        answers: [
                'Five',
                'Thirty',
                'Ten',
                'Seven' 
          ], 
          correctAnswer: 'Seven'
      },
      {
        question: "In the 2017 film 'Get Out,' what items does Missy use to hypnotize chris?",
        answers: [
                'A teacup and a fork',
                'A teacup and a spoon',
                'A plate and a knife',
                'A Glass and a spoon' 
          ], 
          correctAnswer: 'A teacup and a spoon'
      },
      {
        question: "What iconic 1991 horror film involves a cannibalistic serial killer named Buffalo Bill?",
        answers: [
                'The Silence of the Lambs',
                'The People Under the Stairs',
                'Cape Fear',
                'Children of the Night' 
          ], 
          correctAnswer: 'The Silence of the Lambs'
      },
]